Guide to the Knight Kiplinger American statesmen portraiture collection, 1804-2001 MS2375
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Knight Kiplinger American statesmen portraiture collection
1804-2001
1804-1960
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Kiplinger Washington Editors
MS2375
14.5 Linear Feet
This collection contains portraits in the form of lithographs, photographs and paintings of famous Americans and historical events. The materials date between 1804-2001 with a bulk of the collection being undated. Some of the objects corresponding control files with extra information on the object.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
Organized into five series: Lithographs, Photographs, Paintings, Accession files, znc unsorted images.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Kiplinger Washington Editors, May 30, 2017 (2017.026)
Biographical / Historical
The Kiplinger Washington Editors was a family run publishing company in Washington DC. The Kiplinger family collected a large collection of art for the headquarters of the Kiplinger Washington Editors offices near Lafayette Square. Before its transfer, the Kiplinger Collection was one of the largest privately held collections of Washingtoniana. The collection has since been divided between the George Washington University and the Historical Society of Washington DC. GWU received the portraiture portion of the collection.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains portraits in the form of lithographs, photographs and paintings. The objects in the collection date from about 1804-1960 with many undated objects. The accession files date from 1991-2001. These are from the collection of the Kiplinger Washington Editors, Inc.. Materials represent images of famous American politicians from Washington to Kennedy. Included is an almost complete set of small lithographs of every President from Washington to Kennedy, with a few Supreme Court Justices included. There are also several images of the wives of US Presidents, King George VI and Queen Elizabeth, military persons, and other major events and people from US History.
Some objects have a corresponding accession file which provides information about the objects. This file number can be found in the object note. Not all objects have files.
Presidents; United States presidents; Presidents' spouses; Lithographs
- Lithographs, 1804-1972; Series 1
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains lithographs, envelopes and election material. The contents date between 1804-1972 with the bulk of the material being undated.
  Arrangement
  The material is arranged alphabetically.
  - Andrew Jackson, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    General
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.2801.U.
  - Andrew Johnson, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.1583.U.
  - Andrew Johnson, Davy Crockett, Undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.4552.u, PR.PO.M.580.u.
  - Benjamin Harrison, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.1572.U.
  - Calvin Coolidge, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.1574.U.
  - Calvin Coolidge, Undated; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.4575.u.
  - Charles E. Hughes, 1940; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.4594.U.
  - Chester A. Arthur, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.1579.U.
  - Coolidge, Undated; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.3255.u.
  - Daniel Webster, Undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.2948.U.
  - Daniel Webster, Undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Accession file number MR.PO.L.2954.U.
  - Daniel Webster, Undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.2943.U.
  - Debating in the Senate Chamber, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.3139.U.
  - Edward D. White, 1940; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.4591.U.
  - Eisenhower, Undated; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.3241.u.
  - Eisenhower, Undated; Series 1 (Map-folder 2)
    Accession file number MR.PO.E.3279.
  - For President Warren Harding, Undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Accession file number BS.PO.E.4558.u.
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.1569.U.
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt, Undated; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.4574.u.
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt, Undated; Series 1 (Map-folder 3)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt, Henry Clay Ribbon, Presidents of the United States, Polk Elected annoucement, Undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Accession file numbers PR.PO.E.4559.u, FA.PO.S.455.AF, PR.PO.L.455.BF, BR.PR.L.455.CF.
  - Franklin Pierce, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.1586.U.
  - Franklin Pierce, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.2940.U.
  - Franklin Pierce, Undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.2938.U.
  - Fred M. Vinson, 1940; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.4581.U.
  - General Curtis envelope, Seymour and Blair ballot, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Accession file numbers PR.PO.S.4477.U, BS.EL.S.2495.F.
  - George Washington, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.2797.U.
  - Grover Cleveland, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.3138.U.
  - Harlan F. Stone, 1940; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.4593.U.
  - Harry S Truman, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.1571.U.
  - Harry Truman, Undated; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.3250.u.
  - Henry Clay Silhouette, 1930; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.2901.u.
  - Herbert Hoover, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.1567.U.
  - Hon. William H. English, Undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.4494.U.
  - Hoover, Undated; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.3254.u.
  - J. Garfield, 1899; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.3218.u.
  - J. Q. Adams, Undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.2830.A.U.
  - James K. Polk, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.3140.U.
  - James Buchanan, 1961; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.1599.U.
  - James Buchanan, Rutherford B. Hayes., Undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.2851.U, PR.PO.L.0677.f.
  - James A. Garfield, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.1581.U.
  - James K. Polk, James Monroe, Undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.2925.u, PR.PO.L.613.f.
  - James Madison, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.2804.U.
  - James Madison, Undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.4577.U.
  - James Monroe, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.2805.U.
  - Jefferson, 1960; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.3249.u.
  - John Adams, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.28082.U.
  - John Brown envelope, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Accession file number PR.PO.S.25.U.
  - John Q. Adams, Undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.2831.U.
  - John Quincy Adams, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.2806.U.
  - John F. Kennedy, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.1570.U.
  - John Jay, 1940; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.4582.U.
  - John Marshall, 1804; 1950; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.4506.U.
  - John Rutledge, 1940; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.4584.U.
  - John Tyler, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.1589.U.
  - Johnson/Goldwater, Undated; Series 1 (Map-folder 1)
    Accession file number MR.PO.E.4564.U.
  - Justice Taft, Undated; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.3265.u.
  - John Tyler, Undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.2927.u.
  - John Tyler, Undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.2928.u.
  - Kennedy, Undated; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.3253.u.
  - Martin van Buren, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.2800.U.
  - Martin Van Buren, Grover Cleveland, 1957; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.2853.u, 692.
  - McKinley, Undated; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Melville W. Fuller, 1940; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.4590.U.
  - Memorial Service of James Garfield, Undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.4189.U.
  - Millard Fillmore, Undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.2921.u.
  - Millard Filmore, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.1587.U.
  - Morrison R. Waite, 1940; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.4589.U.
  - Nixon, Undated; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.3256.u.
  - Oliver Ellsworth, 1940; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.4585.U.
  - Our Martyred Presidents, Undated; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.3117.u.
  - President McKinley and His Cabinet, Undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Accession file number MR.PO.L.311.U.
  - President McKinley and his Cabinet, Undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.3120.u.
  - Presidents of the United States, 1853; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.3114.u.
  - Republican Ticket Garfield and Arthur, For President Millard Filmore, 1880; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Accession file numbers 5197.PL.S.U, FA.PO.M.2511.F.
  - Richard Mentor Johnson Silhouette, 1932; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.2979.u.
  - Rutherford B. Hayes, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.1580.U.
  - T. Jefferson, 1805; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.2876.u.
  - T. Jefferson, John Adams, 1899; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    Accession file numbers PR.PO.L.2827.u, PR.PO.L.562.F.
  - T. Roosevelt, Undated; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.3245.u.
  - Taft, Undated; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.3244.u.
  - Theodore Roosevelt, Undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Accession file number MR.PO.L.2549.u.
  - Theodore Roosevelt, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.1573.U.
  - Theodore Roosevelt, 1915; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.3291.U.
  - Thomas Jefferson, 1961; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.2803.U.
  - Ulysses Grant, Undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Accession file number MR.PO.L.3227.U.
  - Ulysses Grant, Undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Accession file number PR.PO.E.3225.U.
  - Ulysses S. Grant, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.1582.U.
  - Uncle Sam, Undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Accession file number PR.CA.L.4573.U.
  - Unknown Gentleman by Roche, Undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.4536.U.
  - Vanity Fair Sovereigns, No. 10, 1972; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.3219.u.
  - W. H. Harrison, Undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.2917.u.
  - Warren G. Harding, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.1578.U.
  - We Mourn Our Loss (Taft), 1931; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Accession file number MR.PO.L.3290.u.
  - William J. Bryan and John W. Kern postcard, 1908; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Accession file number MR.PO.S.2909.U.
  - William Henry Harrison, 1961; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.1590.U.
  - William Howard Taft, 1940; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.4592.U.
  - William Howard Taft, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.1575.U.
  - William McKinley, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.1568.U.
  - William McKinley, Undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Accession file number MR.PO.L.3266.U.
  - Wilson, Undated; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.3252.u.
  - Wilson Vanity Fair, Undated; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    Accession file number MR.PO.L.3263.u.
  - Woodrow Wilson, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.1577.U.
  - Zachary Taylor, 1961; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.1588.U.
  - Zachary Taylor, Benjamin Harrison, Undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.2922.u, 693.
- Photographs, 1932-1958; Series 2; 9.75 Linear Feet
  This series contains photographs. The contents are dated between 1932-1958 but the majority are undated.
  - Benjamin Harrison, James Blaine and electoral results, Undated; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Accession file number PH.PO.L.3238.U, PP.EL.M.2513.AF, PP.EL.M.2513.BF.
  - Chief Justices of the Supreme Court of the US, Undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Accession file number MR.PO.L.3275.U.
  - Congress, Undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Accession file number PH.AG.L.11229.U.
  - Congress, Undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Accession file number PH.AG.L.1228.U.
  - Debating in the Senate Chamber, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Accession file number MR.AC.L.2981.U.
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower, Undated; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Accession file number PH.PO.S.4381.U.
  - Dwight Eisenhower, 1958; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Accession file number BS.PO.L.4548.u.
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt, 1932; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Accession file number MR.PO.M.3236.U.
  - Franklin Pierce, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - George VI and Queen Elizabeth, Undated; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Accession file number PH.PO.L.4181.U.
  - General Leonard Wood, Undated; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Accession file number PH.PO.L.4598.U.
  - Harold Ickes, 1940; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Accession file number PH.PO.M.3121.U.
  - James Farley, Undated; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Accession file number MR.PO.L.2975.u.
  - JFK Funeral, Undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Accession file number PH.AC.L.1121.U.
  - Lincoln, Undated; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Accession file number PH.PO.L.1118.u.
  - Martin Luther King Jr., Undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Accession file number MR.PO.L.2976.U.
  - Mrs. Benjamin Harrison, Undated; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Accession file number PH.PO.M.2860.U.
  - Mrs. Cleveland, Undated; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Accession file number PH.PO.M.2854.U.
  - President Grant, Undated; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Accession file number PH.PO.L.3214.u.
  - President Grover Cleveland, Undated; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Accession file number PH.PO.M.3239.U.
  - President Taft and others, Undated; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Accession file number PC.90.S.3129.U.
  - Swearing In, Undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    Accession file number PH.AC.L.2962.U.
  - Taft, Undated; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Accession file number 4549.
  - Taking the Oath of Office, Undated; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Accession file number MR.AC.L.3234.u.
  - The President and Cabinet, Undated; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Accession file number PH.PO.M.3128.U.
  - The Senate in Session, Undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    Accession file number PH.AG.E.4542.U.
  - Theodore Roosevelt, Undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Accession file number MR.PO.L.3264.u.
  - Unknown, Undated; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Accession file number PH.PO.L.3257.u.
  - Unknown, Undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Accession file number PH.PO.L.2905.U.
  - Warren G. Harding and Calvin Coolidge, Undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Accession file number MR.PO.L.3229.U.
  - Woodrow Wilson, Undated; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Accession file number MR.PO.L.3262.u.
- Paintings, Undated; Series 3; 1.75 Linear Feet
  This series contains paintings. The material is undated.
  - Andrew Jackson, Undated; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.2932.U.
  - James Madison, Undated; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Accession file number PR.PO.E.4576.U.
  - J. Q. Adams, Undated; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.2830.B.U.
  - McKinley?, Undated; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Accession file number PR.PO.M.3203.U.
  - Unknown, Undated; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.2950.U.
  - Unknown, Undated; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Accession file number PR.PO.L.2959.U.
- Accession files, 1991-2001; Series 4; 2.5 Linear Feet
  The material is arranged numerically.
  This series contains the accession files for the objects in the other series. The objects accession file number is recorded at the folder level in a note. The material dates between 1991-1996.
  - FA.PO.S.455.A.F, 1994; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - BR.PR.L.455.C.F, 1994; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - PR.PO.L.562.F, 1994; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - PR.PO.L.613.F, 1994; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - PR.PO.L.613.F, Undated; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - PR.PO.L.677.F, Undated; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - PR.PO.L.693.F, 1994; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - PR.PO.M.1588.U, 1996; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - PR.PO.M.1590.U, 1996; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - PR.PO.1599.U, 1996; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - FA.PO.M.2511.F, 1992; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - PP.EL.M.2513.A.F, 1995; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - PR.PO.M.2803.U, 1991; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - PR.PO.L.2827.U, 1992; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - PR.PO.M.2852.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - PR.PO.L.2876.U, 1992; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - PR.PO.L.2901.U, 1992; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - PR.PO.L.2979.U, 1992; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - PR.PO.L.3218.U, 1992; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - PR.PO.L.3114.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - PH.PO.M.3121.U, 1991; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - MR.PO.E.3226.u, Undated; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - MR.PO.M.3236.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - PR.PO.L.3249.U, 1992; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - MR.PO.E.3279.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - MR.PO.L.3290.U, 1992; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - PH.PO.M.4381.F, 1992; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - PR.PO.M.4589.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - PR.PO.M.4584.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - PR.PO.M.4586.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - PR.PO.M.4590.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - PR.PO.M.4591.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - PR.PO.M.4592.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - PR.PO.M.4594.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - PR.PO.M.4582.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - PR.PO.M.4581.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - PR.PO.M.4593.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - PR.PO.M.4585.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - PH.PO.L.1118.U, 1994; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - PR.PO.L.316.F, 1994; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - PR.PO.L.317.F, 1994; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - PR.PO.L.331.F, Undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - PR.PO.E.598.F, Undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - PR.AC.E.60.F, 1994; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - PR.PO.L.615.F, Undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - PR.PO.L.618.F, Undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - PR.PO.L.623.F, 1995; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - PR.PO.L.624.F, Undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - PR.PO.L.639.F, Undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - PR.PO.L.640.F, 1994; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - PR.PO.L.643.F, 1994; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - PR.PO.L.668.F, Undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - PR.PO.L.676.F, 1992; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - PR.PO.M.679.A.F., 1994; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - PR.PO.S.679.B.F., 1991; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - PR.PO.S.679.C.F., 1994; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - PR.PO.S.679.D.F., 1994; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - PR.PO.S.679.F, 1994; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - PR.PO.L.682.F, Undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - PR.PO.M.931.F, 1988; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - PR.PO.L.985.F, Undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - PR.PO.L.1029.F, Undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - PR.PO.L.1030.F, Undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - PH.EL.S.2494.F, 1996; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - PR.EL.M.2503.A.F, 1991; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - PR.EL.L.2504.F, 1988-1989; Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - PR.EL.E.2505.F, Undated; Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - PR.EL.L.2507.F, Undated; Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - PR.EL.L.2509.F, 1988-1989; Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - PR.CA.L.2526.F, 1988-1989; Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - MR.PO.L.2823.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - PR.PO.L.2871.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - PR.PO.L.2879.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - PR.PO.M.2889.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - PR.PO.E.2944.F, 1993; Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - PR.PO.E.2956.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - PR.PO.E.2961.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - 2970.PR.PO.L.F, Undated; Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - PR.PO.L.2984.U, 1995; Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - BS.GE.L.4161.U, 1992; Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - BS.PO.E.4545.F, Undated; Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - PR.AG.E.4684.F, 1995; Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - 4823.PH.PO.E.F, Undated; Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - PR. PO. 25. U, 1994; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - PR.PO.L.455. B.F., 1992; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - PR.AG.M.550.F, 1994; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - BS.PO.E.603.F, 1991; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - PR.PO.L.692.F, 1994; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - PH.AC.L.1121.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - PH.AE.L.1128.U, 1994; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - PH.AG.L.1129.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - PH.AC.E.1135.F, 1995; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - PR.PO.M.1567.U, 1991; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - PR.PO.M.1568.U, 1991; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - PR.PO.M.1569.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - PR.PO.M.1570.U, 1991; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - PR.PO.M.1571.U, 1991; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - PR.PO.M.1572.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - PR.PO.M.1583.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - PR.PO.M.1574.U, 1991; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - PR.PO.M.1575.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - PR.PO.M.1577.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - PR.PO.M.1578.U, 1997; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - PR.PO.M.1579.U, 1991; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - PR.PO.M.1580.U, 1991; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - PR.PO.M.1581.U, 1991; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - PR.PO.M.1582.U, 1991; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - PR.PO.M.1583.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - PR.PO.M.1586.U, 1991; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 26)